all right today's video is a little bit
of a rant except not I just find it
funny
I keep posting things on Twitter that
like there was part of me who's like
this is gonna go viral and it's gonna
get the thing done and we're gonna get
the global cooperative and they never
even get one like like not even like
nobody retweets them no one likes them
I'm like it's no one's seeing them
meanwhile I see tons of people who
comment you know like they're they have
500 followers and they comment something
like like I don't vaccinate my kid or
all abortions murder and they have tons
and tons of comments and interactions
and like that's why these people do that
so they'll get lots and lots of
interactions or not it just so happens
they're not that way but today I tweeted
it I was like I'm gonna see I just
tweeted capitalism sucks
or stupid that was what it was
capitalism is stupid and three people
retweeted it right away and like six
people liked it which is more than most
of my content good like I don't I don't
know what to do but that is the sea-ice
women I don't know I don't know how to
create the global cooperative
I just know what's gonna happen and
there are things ruminating on what the
next step is it doesn't involve my
tweets going viral clearly because
they're never going to doesn't involve
me going viral on YouTube because if
that's what I was relying on it's
probably not gonna happen but it's just
funny it's like I'm just gonna tweet
this out there I was expecting you'll be
like what do you mean it sucks and how
it started dialog who it is like yeah it
does suck it is stupid retweet whereas I
went about the g7 I was like instead of
these leaders coming in and doing having
pain are spending our taxpayer money and
holding conferences that they're never
going to abide by and someone can just
come in and undo why don't we the people
from Japan and Germany and Italy and
Canada and United States and blah blah
all seven get together and create a the
tools to actually be able to collaborate
and create real solutions crickets
crickets on the comments I make on
YouTube videos on Twitter like about
just the worst communicator too but like
get what I'm trying to say I get that
people don't see my vision of what a
tech cooperative could mean and I don't
need everyone to see the vision I need a
few people to see the vision but just
funny
capitalism is stupid so is your
algorithm goodnight and I will see you
tomorrow